http://www.vilagradwines.co.nz/about/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Vilagrad Wines Ltd always respects your privacy. Our Privacy Policy is explained below, and this relates to any detail we collect about you; whether it’s online or over the phone, also how we use, store or distribute that information.
Now for the details
The following Privacy Policy is to provide a clear and concise outline of how and when personal information is collected, used, stored, and distributed by Vilagrad Wines Ltd. This policy applies to detail collected via the Vilagrad Wines Ltd website: www.vilagradwines.co.nzor any other form. Vilagrad Wines Ltd is bound by the NZ Privacy Act 1993. For more information, visit www.privacy.org.nz
Collection and use of personal information
Vilagrad Wines Ltd collects limited personal information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”) such as: (i) name, mailing and email addresses; (ii) residential address, city, state, postcode, area code, gender, age, purchase history, date and place of purchase. If you communicate with us by e-mail, or complete online forms, surveys or contest entries, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information. For example, we may request personal information from you when you:
contact us for further information;
participate in surveys and other types of research;
enter a promotion,
subscribe to our mailing list;
register your details on our web site;
ask for a quote to be prepared;
express interest in a particular product or service
Other information we may collect
For statistical purposes we collect anonymous information on web site activity (such as top pages viewed, the number of pages viewed, the number of sessions, most popular session times). We use this data to evaluate our web site performance and to improve the content we display to you.
To evaluate the effectiveness of our online advertising (including click throughs from email marketing), we may use third parties to collect statistical data. No personal information is collected on these occasions.
Use of cookies
Vilagrad Wines Ltd may use tracking technologies such as cookies to recognise your browser each time it visits our site, and to track which pages you visit whilst on our site. We may use this information to optimize our site and create a better online experience for you.
Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to a computer's hard disk for record keeping purposes. Most web browsers are set to accept tracking technologies such as cookies. These tracking technologies do not themselves personally identify users, although they do identify a user's browser. However, if you do not wish to receive any cookies, you may set your browser to refuse them.
Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites on the internet.
Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to this website.
You have the option to opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page: http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/ Alternatively you can opt out of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
How we use your information
Vilagrad Wines Ltd uses your information to better understand your exact needs and provide you with better service. Vilagrad Wines Ltd may share your Personal Information amongst related bodies corporate of Vilagrad Wines Ltd.
Vilagrad Wines Ltd may also use your Personal Information:
to deal with your queries or customer service issues whether by email, telephone or mail. We may also keep information on your communications with our customer service representatives.
to keep you up-to-date with products, services, events or promotions we think would be of particular interest through a variety of channels. You  will be able to "opt-out" from this activity at any time.
to enhance your customer experience and help us complete your  transactions faster.
for planning, product development or research purposes.
Disclosure of personal information
We will only send Personal Information to third party organisations when:
we have your consent to share the information;
we need to share your information in order to provide the product or service you have requested;
we need to send your information to companies that are contracted to Vilagrad Wines Ltd, e.g. mailing houses, IT service providers, service providers (e.g. assemblers, repairers), web developers, marketing  agencies, finance companies; or
we are required or authorised by law to disclose the information.
Such information remains under Vilagrad Wines Ltd custodianship at all times and the agents involved are bound by specific confidentiality and non-disclosure agreements.
Access and correction
You can have access to the personal information we hold about you. Our goal is to ensure that your personal information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. To assist us with this, please contact our Privacy Officer if any of the details you have provided change. Further, if you believe that the information we have about you is not accurate, contact us and we will use all reasonable efforts to correct the information. A $25 administration fee will be charged for the retrieval of personal information to cover our costs. No fee applies to the correction of personal information.
Third-party web sites
Links to third party web sites on www.vilagradwines.co.nz are solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave Vilagrad Wines Ltd website. Vilagrad Wines Ltd is not responsible for any of these sites, their content or their usage of your personal information.
Unsubscribe/Opt Out
At Vilagrad Wines Ltd we only want to communicate with you if you want to hear from us. If you would like to unsubscribe from receiving email Newsletters , promo’s etc, you can do so at any time, for any reason.
Security
Vilagrad Wines Ltd is committed to ensuring the security of your personal information and we will take all reasonable precautions to protect this information from loss, misuse or alteration.
Changes to this statement
Vilagrad Wines Ltd may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time for any reason. We will publish those changes on our website on this page.
Sunday Lunches
We are open every Sunday for lunch, continuing our family tradition of celebration...
Book Now
Weddings
Let us create the wedding of your dreams at Waikato's number one wedding venue.
Find Out More
Mid Year Xmas Parties
Party the night away and dance to the great live music by resident band.
Book Now
Tours and Tastings
Join our cellar master and vineyard host for an enjoyable learning experience...
Find Out More
Photo Gallery
Harvest festival, dance party, weddings, winery and vineyard, accommodation and much more...
View Gallery
Accommodation
Sit back and relax in the comfort of our deluxe champagne suite, nestled amongst the Vilagrad vines...
Copyright © 2015 Vilagrad Winery  | Trading as Vilagrad Limited  |  Terms of Service  |  Privacy Policy | Off-License
Website by Digital Stream
